This house of ours will be demolished at 12:00 at night.
I never even thought about it.  Let me
tell you from the beginning how this happened.
Look, after the rains come,
we keep these goats inside so that they do not get
sick due to the rain.  Thank God that today
our goats were saved and alive.
Because I slept late at 12:00 in the night, I
woke up late in the morning and when I came upstairs, I saw that
all the tea was still lying there as it was last
night. Look, there was a time like this.  We used to
sleep under these tins.  But we
placed it on top and adjusted it for the goats
so that the
goats could live comfortably in it during the rains.  That's why
I opened a YouTube channel so that
with your love and support I
can build a nice home here.  It has been 5 years since I started
working on YouTube but till now
I have not received any support from anyone on YouTube.  As soon as I
woke up in the morning, I realized that I could
n't find my soap.  It is
kept among the stones worshipped by mother.  So I quickly took out the
soap and started washing my face.
Well, I washed my mouth thoroughly
and after this I washed away the soap with water and
kept it back.  Then I felt like
washing my feet, so I washed them.
When I looked at my face in the mirror, I saw
soap on it.  So I
washed my face again and after that my
face became completely clean.  And when I
asked this goat how my teeth were?  So he
told me that your teeth are becoming dirtier than my teeth.
Whenever I am lying idle at home,
I play F the most.  I do
n't know brother, when will I get rid of this habit.
And when did my 2 hours pass while I was playing F?
I didn't even know.  And
I haven't washed my shoes for 2 months.  So I
washed them and kept them at one place and after this I
again lay down in front of the cooler.  Then when
I came upstairs and looked, I saw that
cleaning was going on upstairs.  As you know,
last time these three were thrown by a monkey and climbed the mountain.
And you want me to
build another new house here for my goats.
So please like the video and
subscribe to the channel.